Hi. Welcome to this course on software engineering. I'm Juno.
大家好 欢迎来到软件工程课程 我是 Juno
I'm Andrew and we are very excited to be guiding you through this course.
我是 Andrew 很高兴能指导这门课程
Wait. Juno, why are we talking about software engineering?
等一下 Juno 我们怎么在讨论软件工程?
You told me that I was here to teach a course for the Data Scientist Nanodegree program.
你明明告诉我 这是数据科学家纳米学位的课程
Okay. I admit data scientists and software engineers have quite different roles.
好吧 我承认数据科学家和软件工程师的角色截然不同
Data scientists are like the researchers or thinkers who explore and model data.
数据科学家就像是探索数据并建模的研究人员或思想家
For data scientists, code is a means to an end.
对于数据科学家来说 代码是达成目的的手段
On the other hand,
另一方面
software engineers are like the builders and
软件工程师就像是
well engineers who make products and write code for production.
制造产品以及编写产品代码的构建者和工程师
Software engineers need to write efficient,
软件工程师需要编写高效
robust, and maintainable code.
可靠 并且易于维护的代码
But, both data scientists and software engineers code and write programs.
但是 数据科学家和软件工程师都需要编写代码和程序
I think I see where you're going with this.
我应该明白你的目的了
We as data scientists write a lot of code,
作为数据科学家的我们编写了大量代码
but we don't always pay attention to things like code structure and maintainability.
但我们并不总是关注代码结构和可维护性等问题
For example, a good software engineer spends
而优秀的软件工程师会花时间
the time to write clean and well-tested code.
编写整洁且经过良好测试的代码
We have a thing or two to learn from them.
他们有些东西值得学习
Yes. As a data scientist,
是的 作为数据科学家
you most likely be working in teams and share code across your organization.
你很可能是在一个团队中工作 会在组织中共享代码
Your insights could influence important business decisions
你的见解可能会影响到重要的业务决策
or you may be building models to use in their product.
或者你可能正在构建产品所需的模型
This makes it crucial that you follow
这要求你必须遵循
a few software engineering practices that ensure your code is clean and reliable.
一些软件工程实践 来确保代码整洁并可靠
You'll improve the efficiency of your workflow,
这样也可以提高工作流程的效率
collaboration in teams, and communication with software developers.
加强团队协作 改善与软件开发人员的沟通
It's true. Software engineering skills will help you
说的很对 软件工程技能可以帮助你
stand out against the competition when applying for data science positions.
在申请数据科学家职位时脱颖而出
Employers want and often expect
雇主希望并且经常会预期
good software engineering skills from their data scientists.
他们的数据科学家也具有良好的软件工程技能
I'm glad I convinced you because we've got
很高兴能够说服你
some awesome projects and exercises in this course.
在这门课程中有一些很棒的项目和练习
By the end, you will have applied a number of useful software engineering practices,
课程最后 你将应用很多有用的软件工程实践
built a Python package,
构建一个 Python 包
and created a Web application.
以及创建一个 Web 应用
Let's take a closer look at what you'll be building.
让我们详细看看将要学习的内容吧